{
    "subject": "resource/Walter_Pitsch",
    "predicate": "ontology/militaryBranch",
    "object": "resource/Waffen-SS",
    "human_readable": "Walter Pitsch served in the Waffen-SS.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.96845543384552,
            "question": "What role did Walter Pitsch play within the Waffen-SS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8565611839294434,
            "question": "Who was Walter Pitsch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8293596506118774,
            "question": "What organization did Walter Pitsch serve in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8199135661125183,
            "question": "What are some primary sources for learning about Walter Pitsch and the Waffen-SS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40424486994743347,
            "question": "How is Walter Pitsch remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31822842359542847,
            "question": "What does Waffen-SS stand for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.267922043800354,
            "question": "Were there any controversies surrounding the Waffen-SS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25395068526268005,
            "question": "During which historical period was the Waffen-SS active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2517930269241333,
            "question": "What were the primary functions of the Waffen-SS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23844610154628754,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of the Waffen-SS?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Walter Pitsch served in the Waffen-SS.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4245_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the primary functions of the Waffen-SS?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4245_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During which historical period was the Waffen-SS active?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4245_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any controversies surrounding the Waffen-SS?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4245_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4245_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Walter Pitsch's service in the Waffen SS, specifically that he was a Hauptscharf\u00fchrer in the Waffen SS and held the position of commander of the 4th Battery, 1st SS Anti Aircraft Battalion. This supports the statement that Walter Pitsch served in the Waffen-SS."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}